[{"answer": "Well, there is obviously a lot of confusion about the information coming out.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "What are you hearing that might be remotely factual?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "That does seem to be the case.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "He will die for the cause if need be and he's going to create as much bloodshed as it takes to try and stay in power, isn't he?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "How much longer can you hold on?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Already here in Libya, it's a completely different case, isn't it?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "That makes this a very dangerous situation, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Certainly is.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "I mean this is sort of potential Armageddon for Libya if any of this actually happens, isn't it?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "I'm sorry.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Can you hear me?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "Well, it certainly is cause for concern for those of us here in New York.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Commissioner Kelly, this is pretty worrying, isn't it?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "Well, I think the risk has been pretty consistent.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "Would you say that the risk now to cities like New York and America is greater than it was in 2001, for example?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "No, not for this.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Do you think the national homeland security threat level should be raised?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "It's possible.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Is that not an increased threat that perhaps they will try something to reinforce that point?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "I think gentleman would be an overstatement.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "This gentleman broke into your house a few -- a couple of weeks ago?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Well, we have described him as mentally ill and he is currently in a lockdown of a psychiatric unit.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "How would you describe him?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Were you there at the time?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Well, my feeling was just simply to react logically.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "What was your feeling when you heard about this?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "You know --", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Evasive, I imagine?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "TONE: Well, as I'm sure you've come to realize with your own celebrity, you get all kinds of fans and all kinds of incidents.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "Do you get a lot of crank people turning up?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Not stalking you.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "You were there stalking me?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "I don't really think of it like that.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "When would you call it?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "I don't -- I don't really leap to the negatives.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "What are the negatives?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Sixteen, yes.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "15 or 17?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "They really talked to me about keeping my feet on the ground and really enjoying every moment and really staying in my gratitude and grace.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "What was the advice they gave you?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "ORGAN: When you have the kind of incident you've had to deal with recently, is any part of you wish you could turn back on the anonymity cloak that you once had?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "-- kind of stop being crossed.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "I'm happy to claim all credit for this, seriously.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Was it you that made it the most paused moment?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "How do you feel -- seriously, you're the most paused woman in the history of movies, that moment.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "TONE: You were in there with the remote?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "I think that the film as a whole, because it's been like, 18, 19 years -- I think the film has actually held up for people and has created a sort of passage for a sexual identification for people, and a way for people to speak about the way that they feel about themselves, the way they want to communicate about their sexuality.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Are you proud of that moment?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "How I became like her was not in a sexual sense.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Because you kind of admired the way she went about her work?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "I think more I was just so shocked and I was embarrassed not to be able to process it alone with him than I was so horrified.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Were you horrified?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "I -- I don't think I've spoken directly to him lately.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Have you talked to him recently?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "I think part of it genuinely is karma.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "ORGAN: Do you think it is karma?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Who knows what you're going to do in there.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Not going to let me in?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "The wonderful thing about this year is there are so many great people in all the categories.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Who do you fancy this year?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "TONE: You know, I think both those films and \"The Fighter\" - these are kind of films that just -- all of them were just so astonishing that I had to watch all of them more than one time.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Which way are you going?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "If could I only watch one film for the rest of my life, it's probably not a film from this year.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "If you could only watch one again the rest of your life, what would it be?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "I'm a huge Bertolucci fan.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "What would be the movie?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Well, I have to get in there.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Are you going to be on the carpet on Sunday?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "That's how you get in.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "Do you like it?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "You know, I don't really think about it like that anymore, because this has been my life for so long.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Billion of people around the world going, what's she wearing?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "I don't really to have get back to you about the men in my life, Piers.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Is there a vacancy?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "I would say all of the above.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Where would you go?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Their just over-anxious about me being alone.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Not true?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "TONE: No.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "You don't look like you've had any scalpel stuff there?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Actually, mine is natural.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Can you?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "I hope not.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Would you ever go under the knife?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "They're really good.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "How are they getting on?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "Well, you know, when I had this bright idea that I should go ahead and pursue this course of action, I was a younger person.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "ORGAN: How are you getting on being a single mom?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "You're trolling here.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Do you need a guy to help you out?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "Look how cute we are.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "What the hell was I wearing?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "Lovely to be here.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "This is going to be the biggest royal story, yes, since Diana and Charles.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "And I'm delighted you've joined our team, because this is the wedding of the century, isn't it?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "This was crunch time.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "And looking at pictures of William and Kate with their first proper royal engagement up in Wales, what did you make of it?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "She is so down to Earth.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "She seems a normal girl, doesn't she?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "I'm going to be covering the wedding for you and for ABC.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "Have you been invited to the wedding?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "I think you're very right.", "docId": "110224pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "Don't we?", "qSentId": 712}]